A.M. Sullivan Papers
A. M. Sullivan Papers
- Writings
  - Published material
    - Books
      - Modern American Poetry with selections by A.M. Sullivan New Jersey Hills, photocopy (Box 22)
      - This Day and Age, 1943; "A limited edition, privately printed for distribution, Christmas 1943 by Dun's Review" (Box 22)
    - Poetry, 1933; undated (Box 22)
    - Reviews
      - Hold Your Hour and Have Another, by Brendan Behan. "The Side Streets of Dublin," Saturday Review, Feb. 8, 1964 (Box 22)
    - Stories
      - "Kerry Don," The Catholic World, Mar. 1963 (Box 22)
- Memorabilia
  - Photographs, 1930s; undated (Box 22)
  - Publicity items for books (Box 22)
  - Reviews about, 1947-1966; undated (Box 22)
  - Writings by others (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous printed material (Box 22)